https://www.condenast.co.uk/privacy/?_ga=1.14097650.495455568.1452159267

Introduction
Condé Nast Britain is a subsidiary of Condé Nast International, a privately-owned company; we publish twelve of the
world's leading multi-media brands in the UK, listed here.
Condé Nast is renowned as the authority on the latest trends in beauty, fashion, interiors and luxury products, and
for influential reporting - from cutting-edge exposés in current affairs to truthful views on travel experiences.
Our portfolio includes VOGUE, GLAMOUR, HOUSE & GARDEN, TATLER, GQ, WIRED, THE WORLD OF INTERIORS, VANITY FAIR, Condé
Nast TRAVELLER, Condé Nast JOHANSENS, GQ Style and LOVE.
Data privacy and protection is very important to us for everyone who uses our products and services, and who entrusts
us with their information. We have written this privacy notice so you can better understand how we collect data,
what we do with it and how we look after it. We will tell you how long we keep data and what happens when we no
longer need it. We will also outline what rights you have over your data and how we protect and facilitate those
rights.
Opting in and out of communications made easy
Sometimes people want to read privacy notices because a business is asking for their permission to contact them for
marketing. They want to be sure that, if they agree, it will be easy for them to withdraw permission in the future.
We want you to be able to opt out as easily as you opted in. Any marketing email we send you will always have an
"unsubscribe" link that will take you off that relevant marketing list. Please remember that you may have subscribed
from another email address; you will only be able to use the link to "unsubscribe" from the address to which the
marketing email has been sent. We make it easy for you to change your preferences for postal marketing as well,
giving clear instructions for opting out on all direct mail.
If you want to change the preferences you have with us for email or for postal marketing, you can use our online form
here.
Contents
What personal data do we collect from you?
How do we use your personal information?
Legal bases for data
processing – what does it mean and how do we use them?
Do we share your information with anyone else?
Do we collect information on children?
How long will we keep your data?
Profiling – what do we mean?
Data security and cross-border transfers
Link to other websites
Your data rights
How to contact us
1. What personal information do we collect from you?
We collect information:
if you contact us about a query or a complaint
We collect the following types of information:
Contact information
When you use or subscribe to one of our services, such as purchasing a print or digital subscription, signing up to
an email newsletter, entering a competition, joining one of our online communities or participating in any of our
research projects, we will ask you to provide information such as your name, email and/or postal address so that we
can provide you with the services requested.
General personal information
When conducting surveys or running competitions, in addition to contact information, we may collect other personal
information such as your gender, date of birth, marital status, etc.
Payment details
When you purchase a product or service from us, such as subscribing to one of our magazines or attending one of our
events, we will also ask you for your payment details in addition to your contact information, in order to secure
payment and to authorise access to our products and services.
Online identifiers
When you visit one of our websites, we collect information about your web visit, such as how long you visited, what
sites you visited or pages you looked at, your IP address and where you were when you visited, what sort of device
you were using when you visited (such as a mobile phone or type of desktop PC, Mac etc), and information identifying
the language used by your Device.
Behavioural data
When you visit one of our websites, we collect data on your online behaviour (eg time spent on website, items clicked
on, etc).
When you buy a product or service from us, such as magazine subscription or a ticket to a Condé Nast event, we will
collect information about what products and services you have bought from us.
When you register for a newsletter or take part in research, we may collect data about your preferences, tastes and
interests.
"Special" categories of data
Sometimes, we may collect data in online surveys on what is called "special categories of data". These could be data
sets such as biometric information (including voice samples, facial recognition, etc), or political opinions,
religion, philosophical beliefs, health, sexual orientation, etc. Whenever we conduct research on these topics, it
is always optional, and we will make sure we have your consent to process this data. We will remind you at the time
of why and how we are processing this data and what additional safeguards are in place for using, storing and
ultimately either deleting or anonymising this data.
2. How do we use your personal information?
At Condé Nast Britain we collect different types of information about people for four main reasons:
To provide personalised services unique to individual users.
So we can monitor and improve the services we offer.
To sell advertising space on our websites. This helps us to keep our websites free for people who visit them.
To market products and services which we think would be relevant to you.
Newsletters
When you sign up to one of our newsletters, you are giving consent for us to use the email address provided to send
you relevant content for the brands you have signed up to. You can withdraw this consent for any newsletter by
unsubscribing at any time.
Advertising
We advertise on our site and in our newsletters to help keep most of the content free. We use cookies and similar
technologies and work with trusted partners so that we can show you advertisements we believe might interest you, to
control the number of times you see an ad and to measure the effectiveness of a campaign. We have a legitimate
interest in using cookies but you can opt in or out of using them at any time. If you are interested and want to
learn more about these, including how to opt out, please see our Cookie
Policy. Please note, opting out of cookies does not mean you will not see any advertisements.
Social Media Advertising
We work with social media networks such as Facebook and Twitter to show you interest-based marketing content from our
brands and selected advertisers if you have viewed a Condé Nast website. Data collected by these social media
networks may also be anonymised and used in aggregate to help improve the quality and effectiveness of our websites
and marketing efforts.
You can limit this kind of tracking and profiling by going your account settings of Facebook and/or Twitter. You can
also find out more about the pixels and cookies we use on our websites by reading our Cookies policy.
We may also participate in Facebook's 'Custom Audience' service from time to time. This service enables Condé Nast to
display to you personalised advertisements when you visit Facebook’s social media platforms. It works by converting
your email address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers that Facebook generates from
email addresses of its users. Where we use Facebook Custom Audiences, we will only include you if you have consented
to receive marketing from us. If you have given us your consent, you can change your mind at any time by
unsubscribing (linked in any email we send you) or by adjusting your preferences in our preference centre.
Research & Insight
We run various user communities, forums and reader panels. We send out research invitations to our research
communities, to people who pay for our products and services and to people who have opted in to receive
communications from us.
We may sometimes use your gender and age range collected during a survey for building "look-a-like" models. This data
is anonymously transmitted to our Data Management Platform (Permutive) and matched with our subscribers and members.
This allows us to provide relevant and targeted advertising. If you are interested and want to learn more about
these, including how to opt out, please see our Cookie Policy.
Please note, opting out of cookies does not mean you will not see any advertisements.
Delivery of goods and services / Customer account management
We will use the information you have provided for the provision of goods and/or services that you have requested and
subsequently communicating with you about those products and services.
Please note too, that when you buy something from us - such as subscription or a ticket to an event - we may contact
you about your registration details, to manage any account or subscription you have with us, or to provide customer
service. This will be the case even if you have opted-out of, or declined to consent to, receiving promotional
emails.
Competitions
When you enter one of our online competitions, we will process your information for the purposes of picking a winner.
If you have opted-in to receiving information from us about our products and services (eg receiving subscriptions
offers, event invitations, signing up for editorial newsletters etc) then we will use the information you provide to
make sure we offer you relevant products and services (based on where you live, your age, gender, tastes,
preferences etc). If you have opted-in to receive news and offers from any competition sponsors, we will share your
information with them.
Further details about this is outlined in the "who do we share information with" with section.
Partnerships programmes
We work with our partners from the world of luxury goods, fashion, travel and retail so that we can present you with
some outstanding offers and opportunities by either email or post. You will only ever receive partner messages from
us if you have actively given permission. We won’t disclose your personal information to anyone, the messages will
come from us and you can unsubscribe at any time from these messages.
Customer queries and complaints
We process any information you provide when dealing with any complaints or enquiries made by you or legally on your
behalf.
3. Legal bases for data processing –
what does it mean and how do we use them?
The law on data protection sets out several different reasons why a company may collect and process your personal
data and it is one of our duties to make sure you understand which of these lawful bases we are using to process
your data.
Consent
In specific situations, we can collect and process your data with your consent:
When you sign up to any editorial newsletter
When you tick a box to receive email from Condé Nast about news and offers
When you tick a box to consent to receive email from Condé Nast on behalf of our partners
We send SMS messages, either from Condé Nast or on behalf of our partners with your consent
When you give us your details to enter a competition
When you participate in any research, this is with your consent
Legitimate interest
In specific situations, we require your data to pursue our legitimate interests in a way which might reasonably be
expected as part of running our business and which does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests:
We personalise the marketing content we provide you
If you have bought a product or service from us, we will also use your details to send you direct marketing
information by email or post, telling you about products and services that we think might interest you
If you have bought a product or service from us we will send you direct marketing on behalf of our partners
We will only use legitimate interest after we have properly evaluated the data processing and conducted a necessary
balancing test. We will also give data subjects the right to object to the processing at any time.
Contractual obligations
In certain circumstances, we need your personal data to comply with our contractual obligations.
For example, when you purchase a print subscription to a magazine, we will keep your name and address to fulfil your
subscription.
Legal compliance
If the law requires us to, we may need to collect and process your data.
For example, we can pass on details of people involved in fraud or other criminal activity affecting us to law
enforcement.
4. Do we share your information with anyone else?
Condé Nast International and its subsidiaries
We may share your personal information:
With our parent company, Condé Nast International
If all or any of our assets (eg a title owned by us) were to be sold to another business, the personal data
relating to that title (eg the subscriber list / newsletter list etc) would be transferred to the new business
owner.
Service providers
We work with service providers to perform some tasks on our behalf. This might include analysis, payments, marketing,
identity management, IT services. This may include personal information and non-personal site usage information to
provide aggregate demographics on our audiences. We may share your personal data with these providers to perform the
necessary tasks. However, they are obliged not to disclose or use it for any other purposes. Any third-party
processing of your data on our behalf will be subject to security and confidentiality obligations consistent with
this privacy notice and applicable law.
Customer research & insight
We may disclose de-personalised data (such as aggregated statistics) about the audience of our products and services
and/or research participants to describe our sales, customers, traffic patterns and other information to prospective
partners, advertisers, investors and other reputable third parties, and for other lawful purposes. These statistics
will never include identifiable personal information.
Law enforcement organisations
Under certain circumstances we may occasionally be required by law, court order or governmental authority to disclose
certain types of personal information and we reserve the right to comply with any such legally binding request.
Marketing partners
With your explicit permission, we may share your information with other companies we are working with, such as
competition sponsors. Whenever we share your information with another company, we will always ask for your
permission, will name the company and will always be clear that your information will be shared with another
organisation.
5. Collecting data on children
We do not knowingly collect and process information from children (anyone under the age of 13). The products and
services we offer are generally aimed at people aged 18 and over.
If you are under the age of 13, we ask that you do not give us any information about you or use our websites.
If you are a parent or guardian of a child under 13 and you if you think that your child has used our websites or
subscribed to a newsletter or provided their information to us without your consent, please contact us at datacontroller@condenast.co.uk and we will delete and/or stop
processing your child’s personal information within a reasonable time.
If you are aged between 13 and 18, we request that you seek your parent or guardian’s permission before providing us
with your information or using our websites or apps.
6. How long will we keep data?
We will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to provide the individual service/s you have
requested, while taking into account any legal requirements and tax and accounting rules. We do not store customer
data for longer than 6 years after the last purchase.
Where you sign up to receive email marketing from us we will retain your e-mail address after you ‘opt-out’ of
receiving emails to ensure that we continue to honour and respect that request. To unsubscribe from marketing emails
at any time, please click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any marketing email and update your account
preferences. You may also use our preference centre to update
what postal or email communications you wish you receive from us.
In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see ‘Your rights’ below for
further information.
In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for
research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to
you.
7. Profiling
We may sometimes use the data you share with us, and that we collect about you when browsing our websites and
products, to personalise our services and to tailor marketing content. For example, we may use information you have
provided to send you information about products we think you may be interested in. If you do not want to receive
this material, you can unsubscribe at any point.
8. Cross-border transfers and security
We make sure that we have appropriate security measures to protect your information and make sure that, when we ask
another organisation to provide a service for us, they have appropriate security measures and follow the same high
standards of security and data protection as we do.
If we or our service providers transfer any information out of the European Economic Area (EEA), it will only be done
with the relevant protection (stated under UK law) being in place.
9. Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites run by other organisations. This privacy notice applies only to Condé
Nast Britain websites‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on any other websites you visit. We cannot
be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you have accessed them using links from
our websites.
We receive commission on some of the links to third party websites offering products and services that we feature on
our websites. We work with a third party to help us attribute e-commerce traffic. You can find out more in our Cookie Policy.
10. Your rights
As a consumer, you have rights when it comes to your data:
The right to be informed. At every point where we are collecting your data, we will inform you of why it
is being collected and how it is being processed.
The right of access. If you wish to see what information we hold on you, you may send us what is called a
Subject Access request. We will require photocopies of two pieces of identification. We will respond within 30
days of receipt of your request. There is no cost to you in requesting to see your data, but please note that we
reserve the right to charge you if you make subsequent requests. You can use the contact details below for a
Subject Access Request.
The right to rectification. We offer the opportunity to amend your personal information by contacting us
using the details below.
The right to erasure. If you wish to cancel all communications with us, we can anonymise or de-identify
your data. Please contact us using the details below. Please make sure you inform us of all email
accounts, profiles, names etc that you may have used with us that you wish to erase.
The right to restrict processing. You can opt-out or restrict the processing of your data by:
Amending your cookie settings in your browser
Unsubscribing from postal and email communications, using our preference centre
Contacting datacontroller@condenast.co.uk
If you are unhappy with the way we have collected and are using your personal data please do not hesitate to contact
us, using the contact details below or by contacting our Data Protection Officer on dpo@condenast.co.uk.
You have the right to complain to a supervisory authority. In the UK this is the Information Commissioner's Office.
Notice to California Customers - Your Privacy Rights
A. Consumer Privacy. The California Consumer Privacy Act, Cal. Civ. Code §1798.100 et. seq.
("CCPA"), grants residents of California certain rights with respect to their Personal Information and requires us
to provide such individuals with certain information, described in this Section X(A).
California residents may exercise the following rights by contacting our Privacy Notice Coordinator by email at
datacontroller@condenast.co.uk or phone at +1 888-914-9661,
PIN: 867 610, or as described at the end of this document:
Know the ways in which we acquire, use, share, disclose and otherwise process your Personal Information
Know the specific pieces of your Personal Information that we hold
Request the deletion of your Personal Information, subject to several exceptions, and
Not to be denied goods or services for exercising these rights
California residents also have the right to opt-out of the "sale" of their Personal Information. We put "sale"
in quotation marks because the CCPA considers some transfers of Personal Information to third parties in
exchange for value as "sales," even if no money changes hands, such as when online identifiers, Device IDs, and
other information is shared with Third Party Businesses to further their own commercial purposes such as
generating profiles about individuals. If we have actual knowledge that a California resident is younger than
16, we will request opt-in consent before selling their Personal Information. Note that we can still share
Personal Information with third parties if those transfers aren’t "sales," such as with our Service Providers.
Depending on the circumstances and which Service you use, we have disclosed the following categories of your
Personal Information for a "business purpose" (as defined in the CCPA) in the preceding twelve (12) months:
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
Professional information
Education information
Inferences drawn from any of the above information categories.
Depending on the circumstances and which Service you use, we have "sold" (as defined in the CCPA) the following
categories of your Personal Information in the preceding twelve (12) months:
Inferences drawn from any of the above information categories, along with the following categories: (i)
financial, medical, or health insurance information; (ii) audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory,
or similar information; (iii) professional information, and (iv) education information.
B. Shine the Light. California’s "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code Section 1798.83, gives
California customers the right to prevent our disclosure of their Personal Information to third parties for those
third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California
customers asking about the business' practices related to disclosing Personal Information to third parties for the
third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose
Personal Information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer
has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. We have such a policy in place.
C. Online Erasure. California’s "Online Erasure" law, Business and Professions Code Sections
22580-22582, requires operators of certain websites and online services to allow registered users who are under the
age of 18 and residents of California to request removal of Content they post. If you fit that description and
posted Content on a section of our Service that is directed to minors, you may request removal of the Content by
contacting our Privacy Notice Coordinator by email at datacontroller@condenast.co.uk or as described at the end of
this document. In response to your request, we may elect to make the Content invisible to other users and the public
(rather than deleting it entirely), in which case the Content may remain on servers we control and/or may be
publicly available elsewhere if a third party copied and reposted the Content.
11. How to contact us
Thank you for reading our Privacy Notice. If you would like to contact us to understand more about our privacy notice
or wish to contact us concerning any matter relating to individual rights and your personal information, then please
email or write to us at:
Email: datacontroller@condenast.co.uk
The Data Controller
Condé Nast Publications,
Vogue House,
Hanover Square,
London,
W1S 1JU
